{
    "id": "bc81c441d08c4446bef910437f72459a",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is both pretty …………………….. intelligent.",
            "description": "The correct conjunction is both...and...",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "as well as",
                "also"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. his illness, he attends office regularly.",
            "description": "In spite of is the correct preposition.",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Despite of",
                "Inspite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is not perfect …………………………, I can’t help liking her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "however",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You cannot go ……………………… you have finished the task.",
            "description": "Either until or till is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "un till",
                "till"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. you do not take the prescribed tablets, you won’t get better.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "In case"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Something must have happened to them ………………………. they haven’t returned yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "as",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. he lacks formal education, he is one of the most intelligent persons I know.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "As",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. it was a good offer, I accepted it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. she had seen you, you would have been in trouble.",
            "description": "If is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "As",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She became angry …………………….. I said a word.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "after",
                "before",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t seen him ………………………… he moved to the US.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She smiled …………………………. she knew everything.",
            "description": "Either as if or as though is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "as if",
                "as though"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}